<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Chris Benz</title>
		<description></description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/rss-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>OSINT Hack the Box - Infiltration</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Chris Benz</dc:creator>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Apart from many of the other challenges on Hack the Box, some of my favorites that I’ve worked on recently have been from 
Hack the Box’s OSINT Challenge category. I’m a big fan of information gathering challenges and find open source intelligence
to be an incredibly interesting topic overall and have found that so far the challenges on Hack the Box do not dissappoint.
The following is a writeup for the Infiltration challenge I recently completed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/journal/osint-hack-the-box-infiltration.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/osint-hack-the-box-infiltration.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>New Years (Security) Resolutions and Review</title>
				
					<dc:creator>Chris Benz</dc:creator>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;As 2020 comes to a close as one of the most exhausting years in recent memory, I figured now might be as good of a time as ever to review some resolutions with regards to security posture. While many of my own resolutions that I procured at the end of 2019 were stopped dead in their tracks this year due to the COVID-19 pandemic (farewell to a desire of travelling more), I discovered some additional ways of improvement I had not thought of in my initial reflection of 2019 by learning more about the threats posed to individuals and organizations from a security perspective, and what we as individuals can do to improve our security posture to protect our data, accounts, and other resources.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/journal/new-years-security-resolutions.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/new-years-security-resolutions.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
